<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE article PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DocBook XML V4.5//EN" "http://docbook.org/xml/4.5/docbookx.dtd">

<article>

  <articleinfo>
    <title>SoCiA User Manual</title>
    <author>
       <firstname>Neil</firstname>
       <surname>Dantam</surname>
       <othername role='mi'>T</othername>
       <affiliation>
          <!-- Valid email...spamblock/scramble if so desired -->
          <address><email>ntd at gatech dot edu</email></address>
       </affiliation>
     </author>

     <!-- All dates specified in ISO "YYYY-MM-DD" format -->
     <pubdate>2013-03-17</pubdate>

     <copyright>
       <year>2008-2013</year>
       <holder>Georgia Tech Research Corporation</holder>
     </copyright>

     <!-- Most recent revision goes at the top; list in descending order -->
     <revhistory>
       <revision>
          <revnumber>0.0.0</revnumber>
          <date>2013-03-17</date>
          <authorinitials>NTD</authorinitials>
          <revremark>Initial Release</revremark>
       </revision>
     </revhistory>

     <abstract>
        <para>
          This is the manual for the SoCiA library.
        </para>

         <para>
           SoCiA implements the CANopen protocol, focusing on control of servo motors.
         </para>

     </abstract>
  </articleinfo>


  <sect1>
    <title>
      Introduction
    </title>

    <para>TODO </para>

  </sect1>
  <colophon>
    <para>This manual is written in Docbook XML.</para>


     <!--<legalnotice>-->
       <para>
         Redistribution and use in source (XML DocBook) and 'compiled' forms
         (SGML, HTML, PDF, PostScript, RTF and so forth) with or without
         modification, are permitted provided that the following conditions are
         met:
       </para>
       <orderedlist>
         <listitem><para>
           Redistributions of source code (XML DocBook) must retain the
           above copyright notice, this list of conditions and the
           following disclaimer as the first lines of this file
           unmodified.
         </para></listitem>
         <listitem><para>
           Redistributions in compiled form (transformed to other DTDs,
           converted to PDF, PostScript, RTF and other formats) must
           reproduce the above copyright notice, this list of conditions
           and the following disclaimer in the documentation and/or other
           materials provided with the distribution.
         </para></listitem>
       </orderedlist>
       <para>
         THIS DOCUMENTATION IS PROVIDED BY THE COPYRIGHT HOLDERS AND
         CONTRIBUTORS "AS IS" AND ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES,
         INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF
         MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE
         DISCLAIMED. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE COPYRIGHT HOLDERS OR
         CONTRIBUTORS BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL,
         SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT
         NOT LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES;
         LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION)
         HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN
         CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR
         OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE OF THIS
         DOCUMENTATION, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH
         DAMAGE.
       </para>
     <!-- </legalnotice> -->
  </colophon>


</article>
